okay guys finally sorry for all the
好，伙计们终于为所有
technical difficulties here well beyond
这里的技术困难远远超出了
our control before I get started full
在我开始吃饱之前我们的控制
disclosure I've been dealing with a
披露我一直在处理
nasty cold if I lose my voice I
如果我失去声音我会讨厌
apologize in advance that may happen so
提前道歉，可能会这样
welcome to the session on Java EE 8 I am
欢迎参加Java EE 8会议
Linda de McHale I'm one of the
琳达·德·麦克海尔我是其中之一
specification leads for the Java EE 8
Java EE 8的规范引线
platform and in this talk I'm going to
平台，在本次演讲中，我将
be talking about the new Java EE 8
在谈论新的Java EE 8
release what we accomplished what some
释放我们完成的工作
of the new features are this is very
新功能是非常
much a high-level overview talk at the
在会议上进行了很多高层概述
end of the talk I'll be giving you a
演讲结束时，我会给你一个
list of pointers to sessions to where
指向会话的指针列表
you can hear about many of the api's
您可以听到许多关于API的信息
from our spec leads in greater depth at
从我们的规格可以更深入地了解
this conference I'm not used to two
这个会议我不习惯两个
windows anymore so I hope I'm not going
窗户了，所以我希望我不会
to fumble this too bad so I'm gonna
弄糟这个太糟糕了，所以我要
start with a brief overview of some
首先简要概述一下
background a little bit of the history
历史背景
of Java EE 8 why it took so long perhaps
Java EE 8为何花了这么长时间
and then the bulk of the talk I'm gonna
然后我要讲的大部分内容
be talking about the jsr s and M ARS
谈论jsr和M ARS
maintenance releases that we addressed
我们解决的维护版本
as goals in Java EE 8
作为Java EE 8中的目标
I'll say a few wrap-up words about our
我会说一些关于我们的总结
current status and our plans for the
当前状态和我们的计划
future if you went to one of the
未来，如果你去了其中之一
keynotes this morning you may have had
今天早上您可能有过主题演讲
heard some things along those lines and
听到了一些类似的话，
then finally I'll leave you with some
最后我会留给你一些
pointers to other presentations so Java
Java的其他演示文稿的指针
EE 8 is the next and probably last step
EE 8是下一步，也可能是最后一步
in the Java EE brand in the development
在Java EE品牌中发展
of the enterprise platform for us here
我们这里的企业平台
at Oracle so the platform has been
在甲骨文公司，因此该平台
getting bigger obviously we have the web
越来越大，显然我们有网络
profile if you don't need the full
如果您不需要完整的个人资料
functionality of the full platform in
完整平台的功能
this release we've kind of we followed a
这个版本我们遵循了
lot of the goals that we set for
我们设定的许多目标
ourselves in Java EE 7 namely a focus on
自己使用Java EE 7，即专注于
web tier technologies making sure we're
网络层技术，确保我们
modernized with the web tier
网络层实现现代化
continuing our trend towards ease of
延续我们的易用性趋势
development largely through leveraging
通过充分利用来发展
the facilities offered by CDI and then
CDI提供的设施，然后
another item that we wanted to address
我们想要解决的另一个项目
for a long time was modernization and
长期以来是现代化
simplification of the security api's so
简化安全API的操作
quick overview of the history here we
在这里我们快速回顾历史
started this work on this release when
在此版本上开始这项工作
we filed a SRS back in 2014
我们在2014年提交了SRS
unfortunately there was a period of
不幸的是有一段时间
hiatus almost a year as some of our spec
作为我们的一些规格中断了将近一年
leads got diverted to higher priority
线索转移到更高的优先级
tasks internally and it looked like we
内部任务，就像我们
weren't making a whole lot of progress
并没有取得太多进展
so in 2016 when our resources again
所以在2016年，当我们的资源再次
freed up we took a step back and we
解放了我们后退了一步，我们
looked at were we really focused
看着我们真的专注吗
appropriately how do we get a release
适当地，我们如何获得释放
out with a high priority items
优先事项
accomplished in the timeframe that we
在我们完成的时间范围内完成
thought we were going to address namely
以为我们要解决的是
by 2017 so what we did was to try to
到2017年，所以我们要做的是
focus on those items that we thought
专注于我们认为的那些项目
were the most important so these were
是最重要的，所以这些是
the original goals for Java EE 8 in
Java EE 8的最初目标是
terms of the jsr s that we that we filed
我们提交的jsr的条款
but after we got over underway we
但是经过我们之后，我们
realized that some of these were less
意识到其中一些较少
important for new trends in the cloud
对于云中的新趋势很重要
and in micro services and perhaps we
在微服务中，也许我们
should down prioritize on those so what
应该优先考虑那些东西
we did was we conducted a Community
我们所做的是我们进行了社区
Survey the goals of this were to
调查此目标是
validate whether our intuitions for how
验证我们的直觉是否
we should refocus we're really
我们应该重新聚焦
appropriate
适当
indeed the survey did we thought that we
确实，调查是否使我们以为
should focus on web tier technologies
应该专注于网络层技术
modernizing for the web tier and that
网络层的现代化
other areas like JMS which was a
其他领域，例如JMS
relatively mature technology that is
相对成熟的技术
less important for cloud environments
对云环境不太重要
the management API that we wanted to
我们想要的管理API
address again the existing
再次解决现有问题
management API well this would have been
管理API，这本来可以
a good modernization of it was not
好的现代化不是
heavily used so we said okay maybe we
大量使用，所以我们说好吧，也许我们
don't want to prioritize there and MVC
不想在那里优先和MVC
which was a new jsr a lot of
这是一个新的jsr
applications in the cloud of course ship
云中的应用程序
headless so MVC seemed to be less of a
无头的所以MVC似乎少了
priority for us well we did with the MVC
我们对MVC的优先考虑
jsr is we hand that off to members of
jsr是我们将其交给
the expert group and that has been
专家组，那是
successfully completed MVC 1o although
尽管成功完成了MVC 1o
it's not part of the Java EE 8 platform
它不是Java EE 8平台的一部分
per se ok so this slide reflects the
好的，所以这张幻灯片反映了
changes that we made dropping the
我们删除了
efforts on JMS and management and then
JMS和管理方面的工作，然后
cutting loose on MVC ok so now I want to
削减对MVC的确定，所以现在我要
get to the meat of this talk which is a
了解这个话题，
survey of the various J afar's
各种J afar的调查
as I said before our focus areas are
正如我在关注重点之前所说的那样
gonna be on web tier enhancements ease
将在网络层上增强功能
of development through leverage of CDI
通过利用CDI进行开发
and then simplification and
然后简化和
modernization around the area of
周边地区的现代化
security so of these most of the focus
安全，所以这些都是重点
was indeed on web tier and leveraging
确实是在Web层并利用
CDI in the process so I want to start
CDI在此过程中，所以我想开始
there ok Jason processing the Jason
好的Jason处理Jason
processing API was introduced as part of
处理API是作为的一部分引入的
Java EE 7 it was the new technology then
Java EE 7当时是新技术
we want it to continue to evolve it to
我们希望它继续发展到
keep pace with emerging standards and
与新兴标准保持同步
there were three standards that were
有三个标准是
produced by IETF that we wanted to track
IETF制作的我们想要跟踪的
and incorporate into the api's for JSON
并合并到JSON的api中
processing namely Jason pointer Jason
处理即Jason指针Jason
patch and Jason merge patch we also
补丁和杰森合并补丁，我们也
wanted to add classes and methods to
想要添加类和方法到
better utilize the java SE 8 stream
更好地利用Java SE 8流
operations so that you could leverage
操作，以便您可以利用
these in in your quote unquote JSON
这些在您的报价中取消引用JSON
queries
查询
okay so Jason pointer it's what its name
好吧，Jason指针，它叫什么名字
suggests it's just a pointer for
表明这只是一个指针
pointing into a Jason document for
指向Jason文档
referencing a JSON value it has a string
引用一个具有字符串的JSON值
based syntax and it's got methods to
基于语法，并且有方法
allow you to extract the value or to use
允许您提取值或使用
the pointer to transform your jason
转换杰森的指针
document with add remove and replace
添加删除和替换的文档
operations so if we look at a simple
操作，所以如果我们看一个简单的
example we're creating a pointer we have
例如，我们正在创建一个指针
a document on adjacent array on our on
在我们的相邻数组上的文档
our right and it's got two elements one
我们的权利，它有两个要素
representing Duke the other representing
代表杜克，另一个代表
Jane they have phone numbers and so on
简，他们有电话号码，依此类推
so we create a pointer the pointer at
所以我们创建一个指针
this point is just a pointer it's not
这只是一个指针，不是
yet referencing into our document so to
仍参考我们的文档
do that we we pass the reference to the
为此，我们将引用传递给
Jason document as an argument to the get
Jason文档作为get的参数
value method of the pointer and then we
指针的value方法，然后我们
use that to extract them sorry we use
用它来提取他们对不起，我们用
that to extract the relevant value so
提取相关值
here's our document again this time I'm
这一次我又是我们的文件
going to use the replace the replace
将要使用替换替换
method of Jason pointer to transform the
Jason指针转换方法
document and I do so in the obvious way
文档，而我这样做的方式很明显
replacing the value of the first element
替换第一个元素的值
of the document with a new mobile phone
新手机检查文档
JSON patch patches itself adjacent
JSON修补程序修补附近的自身
document and it expresses a sequence of
文档，它表示一个序列
operations that you apply to a target
您应用于目标的操作
document and IETF defines the exact set
文件和IETF定义了确切的集合
of these operations namely operations to
这些操作中的
add remove replace to move or to copy so
添加删除替换移动或复制
what you do is use the JSON patch
您要做的是使用JSON补丁
builder methods to create the patch so
生成补丁的构建器方法
you construct the patch and then you
您构建补丁，然后
apply it to the document with the apply
通过Apply将其应用于文档
method
方法
I'm the to Jason array method allows you
我的Jason数组方法可以让你
allows you to do you convert your patch
允许您转换补丁
so here's another example so we use the
所以这是另一个例子，我们使用
patch builder to construct the patch and
修补程序生成器来构建修补程序并
then if I can see this without moving
那我如果不动就可以看到
around so much and then we use the
周围那么多，然后我们使用
replace method - we use the Builder
替换方法-我们使用Builder
method to construct the patch and here
制作补丁的方法
the patch has two operations one to
该补丁有两个操作
replace a value and then the second to
替换一个值，然后第二个
remove the second element of the array
删除数组的第二个元素
now when you execute a patch these
现在，当您执行补丁时，这些
operations are applied in sequence so
操作按顺序应用，因此
the subsequent operations of the patch
补丁的后续操作
can reference what was done in the
可以参考在
previous operations of the patch if
补丁的先前操作，如果
that's what you want so here we build
这就是您想要的，所以我们在这里建立
the patch and then when we apply it the
补丁，然后当我们应用它时
first thing that happens is the
首先发生的是
transformation of the phone and then the
手机的改造，然后
second thing that happens is the removal
第二件事是移除
of the second element so merge patch is
的第二个元素，因此合并补丁是
another one of these IETF standards and
这些IETF标准中的另一个
the way this works is somewhat
这种工作方式有点
differently you basically compare the
不同的是，你基本上比较
value in the patch to the value in the
补丁中的值
original document and then depending on
原始文件，然后根据
how they relate you produce your output
它们如何联系您产生您的输出
so if the if the element that the patch
所以，如果如果该元素的补丁
references is in the original document
参考文献在原始文档中
then you transform the value that's
然后您转换的价值是
referenced if it's not existing in the
如果它不存在，则引用
original document then you add it to the
原始文档，然后将其添加到
document and if it's got a null value
文档以及它是否为空值
then that says remove the element that's
然后说删除元素
there in the document and then finally
在文档中然后最后
I'd like to talk about what we did with
我想谈谈我们所做的
regard to support for sc8 stream
关于对sc8流的支持
operations excuse me
操作对不起
so here we've got we can think of as a
所以在这里，我们可以将其视为
JSON query we're using our contacts
JSON查询，我们正在使用联系人
document again
再次记录
so we're filtering here for those
所以我们在这里过滤那些
elements that are of female gender and
女性的元素和
then we're extracting the names and
然后我们提取名称并
we're collecting the results so notice
我们正在收集结果，所以请注意
that using a built in Java SE collector
使用内置的Java SE收集器
where we're extracting these as a list
我们在其中将它们提取为列表
but the result is a list of strings so
但是结果是一个字符串列表
we're outside the JSON world so the
我们不在JSON世界之外，因此
solution is obviously to introduce
解决方案显然是介绍
specialized JSON collectors so this is
专门的JSON收集器，所以这是
the same query if you will but instead
相同的查询，如果您愿意，而是
of just extracting as strings we're now
只是提取为字符串，我们现在
extracting in terms of a JSON array so
根据JSON数组提取，因此
that you can in general apply subsequent
您通常可以随后申请
operations or continue in the JSON world
操作或继续在JSON世界中
with your results okay do some binding
根据您的结果，可以做一些绑定
this is a new API that we added in Java
这是我们在Java中添加的新API
EE 8 what it is is it's a jax be like
EE 8它是一个jax就像
api to Marshall and unmarshal between
api至马歇尔和之间的元帅
Java objects and JSON documents so it's
Java对象和JSON文档
attended as a natural follow-on to
作为自然的后续活动参加
augment the capabilities of the JSON
增强JSON的功能
processing API so like other mapping API
处理API，就像其他映射API一样
s that we have things Docs B or JPA
如果我们有文件B或JPA
we designed this so that for convenience
我们设计这个是为了方便
one there's a default mapping between
一个之间存在默认映射
the classes and the Java the Java the
类和Java Java
class is an adjacent document and then
类是相邻文档，然后
there's a rich set of customization
有丰富的自定义设置
possibilities so these customizations
这些定制的可能性
can be achieved either through
可以通过以下方式实现
annotations which could apply to could
可能适用于的注释
apply to single properties or fields or
适用于单个属性或字段或
a class level for some of them or if you
其中一些课程的等级，或者如果您
want to do something more general and
想做一些更一般的事情
even more customized than the
甚至比
annotations provide there's a
注释提供了一个
configuration API that you can use to
您可以用来配置API
execute certain transfer
执行一定的转移
nations or customizations at runtime the
国家或自定义项在运行时
other thing I want to mention is when we
我想说的另一件事是当我们
started this work there were already a
开始这项工作已经有一个
number of Jason binding or Jason binding
Jason绑定或Jason绑定的数量
implementations out so we want it to be
实施，所以我们希望它成为
flexible and allow you to choose if you
灵活，让您选择是否
have a preferred Jason binding provider
有首选的Jason绑定提供者
you don't necessarily need to know used
您不一定需要了解二手货
to use the built-in one you can choose
使用内置的，您可以选择
the provider that you would like so a
您想要的提供者
couple of key api's here one is the
几个关键的api在这里是
Jason B builder which is the clients
客户是Jason B Builder
entry point into the binding API and
绑定API的入口点，以及
this gives you operations for setting
这使您可以进行设置操作
the provider implementation and setting
提供者的实现和设置
configuration properties and it's also a
配置属性，它也是一个
factory for the Jason B class and the
杰森B级和
Jason B is an abstraction over the
杰森（Jason B）是
operations of the framework so this
框架的操作如此
gives you your operations of from JSON
为您提供JSON的操作
and to JSON your serialization
并以JSON进行序列化
deserialization operations so a simple
反序列化操作如此简单
example we have two cars we're going to
例如，我们有两辆车要去
put them into a list in Silicon Valley
将它们放入硅谷的列表中
maybe there are just Priuses and Tesla's
也许只有普锐斯和特斯拉
I mean they're pretty common here and
我的意思是他们在这里很常见
then using the JSON B api's we use the
然后使用JSON B API，我们使用
Builder to create an instance of the
生成器创建实例
Jason B class and then with Jason B we
Jason B班，然后和Jason B一起
invoke the to JSON method to serialize
调用to JSON方法进行序列化
these these instances to a adjacent
这些实例到相邻
document I've cheated a little because
我作弊的文件，因为
I've done the pretty formatting a I know
我已经完成了漂亮的格式化
I don't know if that's a built-in
我不知道那是不是内置的
customization or not there's certainly a
定制与否
formatting customization option you can
格式定制选项可以
use so you can do other things there's a
使用，所以你可以做其他事情有一个
default naming for property and fields
属性和字段的默认命名
you can use annotations to change that
您可以使用注释来更改
if you like you can use annotations to
如果您愿意，可以使用注释来
change the null behaviors whether you
无论您是否更改null行为
want or
想要或
don't want nulls to appear in your
不希望空值出现在您的
serialized JSON and then there's a rich
序列化的JSON，然后有一个丰富的
set of customization options and these
一组自定义选项以及这些
run from naming to ordering what
从命名到订购什么
sequence you want things to appear in
您希望事物出现的顺序
null handling what you want to ignore
空处理您要忽略的内容
what you want to bring into your
你想带什么到你的
document or classes formats for data
资料的文件或类别格式
numbers and coding and adapters adapters
编号，编码和适配器
the adapter API lets you define custom
适配器API允许您定义自定义
mapping so you you implement two methods
映射，因此您可以实现两种方法
adapt to json and adapt from json and
适应json并适应json和
then these will get invoked for you so
然后这些将为您调用
here we're using json config we're gonna
在这里，我们将使用json config
you know do our pretty formatting and
你知道我们漂亮的格式和
we're going to use a car adapter that's
我们将使用一个车载适配器
going to do our transformation and then
去做我们的转变，然后
we pass this config to jason be builder
我们将此配置传递给jason be builder
and it will be used when we when we do
当我们这样做时，它将被使用
our serialization and deserialization we
我们的序列化和反序列化
could also specify here again using
也可以使用
builder that we want to use a particular
我们要使用特定的构建器
provider so this is just an intermediate
提供者，所以这只是一个中间
step
步
in the configuration
在配置中
okay so jax-rs has been another really
好的，所以jax-rs确实是另一个
successful API for us there were two key
对我们来说成功的API有两个关键
areas where we wanted to provide
我们想要提供的区域
enhancements in this release one
此版本的增强功能之一
providing a reactive a really reactive
提供反应性
client API leveraging what Java SE eight
客户端API充分利用Java SE的八点优势
at it and then support for server sent
在它，然后支持服务器发送
events server sent events were specified
指定了事件服务器发送的事件
in the HTML html5 standard and then
在HTML html5标准中，然后
there's some other more minor
还有其他一些未成年人
improvements support for Jason B entity
对Jason B实体的改进支持
providers to facilitate your mappings
提供者以帮助您进行映射
and HTTP patch requests so this is the
和HTTP补丁请求，所以这是
way things looked in Java in jax-rs - Oh
Java在jax-rs中的外观-哦
stepping back a little bit in terms of
向后退一点
client api's jax-rs - Oh introduced a
客户端api的jax-rs-哦介绍了
client API that you could use either
您可以使用的客户端API
synchronously or asynchronously in this
在此同步或异步
case we're using it synchronously so you
如果我们同步使用它，那么您
build up a request and then you you
建立一个请求，然后你
issue the request so that's not terribly
发出请求，这样不会很麻烦
interesting but it was a step forward
有趣，但这是前进的一步
and you can specify in the client API
您可以在客户端API中指定
that you want an async invoker rather
你想要一个异步调用者
than a regular invoker and this allows
比常规调用者要多
you to get back your results in terms of
您将获得以下方面的结果
a future
未来
or perhaps more flexibly you can pass a
或者更灵活地可以通过
you can pass a callback to give you
您可以传递回调给您
notification of the results of the of
通知的结果
the request with a completed method here
具有完整方法的请求在这里
or if the request ends in failure then a
或者，如果请求失败，则
failed method so this gives a little bit
失败的方法，所以这给了一点
more flexibility and then you can you
更大的灵活性，然后您就可以
can check the status of this using the
可以使用
future so what Jax rs21 does is it
未来，所以Jax rs21要做的是
offers an improvement over this style
对此样式进行了改进
which gives you more flexibility namely
这给您更多的灵活性
an Rx invoker which gives you back
一个Rx调用程序，它可以将您带回
instead a completion stage so in this
而是完成阶段，因此在此
simple example we're passing a method to
一个简单的例子，我们将一个方法传递给
the completion stage that just basically
基本上就是完成阶段
says print it out that's not terribly
说打印出来不是很可怕
interesting but things get more
有趣，但事情变得更多
interesting when you look at the few the
有趣的是，当你看几个
the real capabilities of completion
真正的完成能力
stages namely that you can execute
可以执行的阶段
multiple requests you can combine them
您可以将多个请求合并
you can sequence them you can choose
您可以选择它们的顺序
which one your you're going to go with
你要去哪一个
and then at the end of the day we're
然后在一天结束时
finally going to accept and print out so
最终将接受并打印出来
in this case what we're doing is we're
在这种情况下，我们正在做的是
taking the the two results the the
取两个结果
completion stage results here we're
完成阶段结果在这里
combining them we're concatenated them
结合它们，我们将它们串联在一起
and we'll get out some kind of printout
我们将打印出某种形式的内容
that looks like hello bonjour at the end
最后看起来像你好卓悦
of the day
今天的
so server-sent events is targeted
因此以服务器发送的事件为目标
allowing the client to subscribe to a
允许客户订阅
sequence of event notifications from the
来自的事件通知顺序
server the way this works is that the
服务器的工作方式是
client establishes a connection to the
客户建立与
server this is an HTTP connection but
服务器，这是一个HTTP连接，但是
it's a long-running connection that's
这是一个长期运行的连接
held until it's closed by the client and
一直保持到客户关闭为止
it's reused for multiple notifications
可以重复用于多个通知
from the server you designate this with
从您指定的服务器
a special media type an event stream
一种特殊的媒体类型，一个事件流
media type and then an event object
媒体类型，然后是事件对象
itself is structured it has a payload
它本身是结构化的，具有有效载荷
which is our corresponds to the data
这是我们对应的数据
field and it has other information a
字段，它具有其他信息
name which can be used if you will to
可以使用的名称
identify a channel perhaps an ID which
识别一个频道或一个ID
you might use for some sequencing
您可能会使用一些测序
operations or keeping track of what's
操作或跟踪内容
coming back retry and comment fields so
回来重试和评论字段，所以
there are two sides to this API in in
该API有两个方面
jax-rs to one the client-side uses these
jax-rs到客户端使用这些
are the most important interfaces at the
是最重要的界面
client side the event source which used
客户端使用的事件源
to open the connection to the web target
打开与Web目标的连接
and then subscribe your consumer it's
然后订阅您的消费者
Auto closable but you can close it
自动关闭，但您可以将其关闭
explicitly and the inbound SSE event
显式和入站SSE事件
which is what you're going to use to
这是您将要使用的
extract the notification that's been
提取已经的通知
sent from the server so on the client
从服务器等客户端发送
side you might have something like this
一边，你可能会有这样的事情
we're constructing we're getting back an
我们正在构建，我们正在恢复
event source and then with us event
事件源，然后和我们一起
source we're registering we're
我们正在注册的源
registering the method that we want to
注册我们想要的方法
have invoked when the event comes in and
事件进入时调用了
then to kick off the flow of
然后开始
notifications from the server we open
来自我们打开的服务器的通知
the connection with the event source
与事件源的连接
open method
开放方法
the server-side has an event sync as you
您在服务器端进行事件同步
might expect this is injected as a
可能希望这作为
recess a parameter to the resource
向资源隐藏参数
method on on the server side the
服务器端的方法
instance corresponds to a single client
实例对应一个客户
HTTP connection and the server uses this
HTTP连接，服务器使用此连接
to send the event to the client SSE is I
发送事件到客户端SSE是我
guess you can think of it as a factory
猜你可以把它当作工厂
class for creating new events or
用于创建新事件的类，或
creating event broadcasters and for
创建事件广播者并
configuring the events so on the server
在服务器上配置事件
you might have a resource method that
您可能有一种资源方法
looks like this so notice that we've
看起来像这样，请注意，我们已经
designated the media type the media type
指定媒体类型媒体类型
is again the text event stream media
再次是文本事件流媒体
type is what the service and events Maps
类型是服务和事件的映射
to and then in our SUBSCRIBE method
到然后在我们的SUBSCRIBE方法中
we've injected the event sync and we've
我们注入了事件同步，并且
injected this SSE factory method and
注入了此SSE工厂方法并
then we're using the event sync to send
然后我们使用事件同步发送
the new event over to the client
新事件移交给客户
another big-ticket item that we're
我们的另一个高价商品
addressing in the servlet API and
在servlet API中寻址
servlet for oh because this was a fairly
servlet哦，因为这是一个相当
major undertaking was support for the
主要任务是支持
new HTTP protocol this is another recent
新的HTTP协议，这是另一个最近的协议
standard from IETF and the goals of HTTP
IETF的标准和HTTP的目标
2 are to overcome the limitations of the
二是克服局限性
existing HTTP one-one protocol namely to
现有的HTTP一一协议即
reduce latency to support parallelism
减少延迟以支持并行
without requiring you to have multiple
不需要你有多个
connections as a workaround to achieve
连接作为解决方法
parallelism to address the head of a
并行处理一个头
head of line blocking problem basically
线头阻塞问题基本上
many performance improvements while
同时改善了许多性能
retaining the semantics of HTTP 1 1 so
保留HTTP 1 1的语义，因此
this looks more or less transparent and
这看起来或多或少是透明的，
what makes this work there's
是什么使得这项工作的
request/response multiplexing over a
请求/响应多路复用
single connection with a binary framing
具有二进制框架的单连接
layer and the binary framing layer
层和二进制框架层
allows the frames which are sent over
允许发送过来的帧
this connection to be identified as
此连接被标识为
which streams they correspond to so that
它们对应于哪些流，以便
you can so that you can demultiplex on
您可以这样就可以在
their receiving in and extract the
他们的接收并提取
stream of messages that that are a
消息流是
consistent stream of messages
一致的消息流
it also can contains a server push API
它还可以包含服务器推送API
so the server can optimize by pushing
因此服务器可以通过推送进行优化
data to the client in advance of the
提前向客户发送数据
clients request for it so then the
客户要求它，然后
client can cache this information so for
客户端可以缓存此信息，以便
example if you're sending over the data
如果您要发送数据的示例
that's been requested for an HTML page
HTML页面已被请求
you know or you can anticipate that
你知道或者你可以预期
maybe you want to send the CSS data
也许您想发送CSS数据
early on you want to push that out or
您想尽早将其推出或
you want to push out other needed
你想推出其他需要的
information before before other
先于先知
information
信息
there's also facilities for header
也有标头设施
compression to again make this protocol
压缩以再次使该协议
more efficient so this was the
更有效，所以这是
big-ticket item for
的大件物品
servlet for Oh support for HTTP to the I
servlet哦，对I的HTTP支持
believe the there's a talk on servlet
相信关于servlet的话题
for Oh later in this conference I'll
因为在这次会议的后面，我会
give you the pointer I believe the the
给你的指针，我相信
main or only user application visible
主或唯一用户应用程序可见
feature here is the server push API so
这里的功能是服务器推送API，因此
that you can configure your pushes on
您可以配置您的推送
from your servlet and that looks
从您的servlet，看起来
something like this there's a push
像这样的东西有推动
builder API so you can construct the
构建器API，因此您可以构建
push referencing what you want to push
推送引用您要推送的内容
and then headers or other other
然后是标题或其他
information that are appropriate for the
适用于
transmission of the push and then you
传播的推动，然后你
can push this out to the client JSF is
可以将其推出客户端JSF是
certainly a mature technology this was a
当然，这是一项成熟的技术
2.3 release which I think indicates that
2.3发布，我认为这表明
I'm not going to say much here except um
除了嗯，我在这里不多说
the expert group addressed an enormous
专家组的演讲
number of smaller feature requests and
较小的功能请求数和
JIRA items when I initially prepared the
我最初准备JIRA物品时
slide the spec Lee told me that
李告诉我，
something like 600 some JIRA items had
大约有600个JIRA物品
had been resolved in this release so
已在此版本中得到解决，因此
certainly non-trivial from that point of
从那一点来看肯定是不平凡的
view but some of the things that this
认为这只是一些事情
contains are improved integration with
包含改进的集成
CDI support for WebSocket integration
CDI支持WebSocket集成
Ajax method invocation and then
然后调用Ajax方法
leveraging being validation and the new
利用验证和新
date/time support
日期/时间支持
okay so speaking of cd-i which is a key
好吧，说到cd-i这是一个关键
technology for us
我们的技术
CDI 200 was a big release but one of the
CDI 200是一个很大的版本，但其中之一
main focus areas of CDI was not so much
CDI的主要关注领域不是很多
Java EE as providing support for use of
Java EE为使用提供支持
CDI outside of Java EE namely with a
Java EE外部的CDI，即
bootstrap API to let you bootstrap a CDI
引导程序API，可让您引导CDI
container in SZ environments the expert
SZ环境中的集装箱专家
group wisely split the spec into three
明智地将规格分为三部分
parts when they were doing this a core
当他们这样做时是核心
CDI which is used both in EE and SC
在EE和SC中都使用的CDI
environments and then those api's that
环境，然后是那些api
are specific for use in SE environments
专门用于SE环境
like this bootstrapping api and then
像这样的自举API，然后
those api's that are used more in Java
Java中使用更多的api
EE think session beans because CDI does
EE认为会话bean是因为CDI
in fact speak of EJB session beans and
实际上，谈到EJB会话bean和
how they're used in CDI from an EE
如何在EE的CDI中使用它们
perspective I'm going to talk here
角度我要在这里说
mostly about the improvements that were
主要是关于
made in observers and events there were
由观察者和事件
a number of other features that were
还有许多其他功能
done annotation literals which are an
完成的注释文字是
ease of use capability alignment with
易于使用的功能与
some of the new SC features the stream
一些新的SC功能具有流
API repeating annotations lambdas use of
API重复注释lambda使用
completion stage and many enrichments to
完成阶段和许多丰富的
the the CDI spi okay
CDI SPI好吗
events and observers this is what things
事件和观察者这是什么东西
look like in CDI 1:1 or EE Java EE 7 you
看起来像在CDI 1：1或EE Java EE 7中
construct an event and you fire it and
构造一个事件，然后触发
when you fire it the observers are
当你开火时，观察者
invoked synchronously there they're
他们在那里同步调用
invoked in the same thread as the fire
在与火相同的线程中调用
method and they're invoked in whatever
方法，它们在任何情况下都被调用
order the CDI container chooses to
订购CDI容器选择
invoke them in
调用它们
in CDI to OCD I made two improvements
在CDI转换为OCD方面，我做了两项改进
here first of all it gives you the
首先，它给你
ability to order synchronous events
订购同步事件的能力
using the priority annotation so
使用优先级注释
priorities and annotation in common
优先事项和注释相同
annotations it didn't use to apply to
不适用于的注释
two parameters we updated the common
我们更新了两个参数的共同点
annotations with an M R so that you
带有MR的注释，以便您
could do this and now you can order your
可以做到这一点，现在您可以订购
observers so that you know when an
观察者，以便您知道何时
observer triggers if you want to
观察者触发，如果你想
leverage what was done in that observer
利用在该观察者中所做的事情
you have this determinism the other
你有这种确定性
improvement that was made was support
所做的改进是支持
for asynchronous events so when you fire
用于异步事件，因此当您触发
an event asynchronously you're
异步事件
guaranteed that there's at least one or
确保至少有一个或
more threads that are going to be used
更多将要使用的线程
for for the firing of the observer
为解雇观察员
methods that are responding to this
对此作出响应的方法
event and the way you designate those
事件以及您指定这些事件的方式
observer methods is with the observes a
观察者方法与观察者
sync with the observes they sync so as
与他们同步的观察同步
you might expect it would be non
您可能希望它不会
portable to specify priority with a sync
可移植以通过同步指定优先级
observers because of the nature of being
观察者，因为存在的本质
async you're not going to be able to
异步，您将无法
order them in any deterministic way so a
以任何确定性的方式订购它们，以便
couple of things to note with this one
这件事要注意的几件事
the same type of event can be fired both
可以触发相同类型的事件
synchronously or asynchronously
同步或异步
but the observers that are eligible for
但有资格参加的观察员
being notified of the event depend on
被通知事件取决于
whether they are synchronous observers
他们是否是同步观察者
which would be notified for a
将会收到通知
synchronous event or asynchronous
同步事件或异步
observers which would be notified for
观察员将被通知
the asynchronously fired event with an
异步触发的事件
asynchronous observer is called in a new
异步观察者在新的方法中被调用
life cycle context and it and a new
生命周期上下文及其新
transaction context so they can't be
交易环境，因此它们不能
transactional in the sense of the
交易意义上的
synchronous observers okay how am i
同步观察者好吧我怎么样
doing on time
准时做
okay beam validation so this is another
好的光束验证，这是另一个
two oh I think for good reason it
两个哦，我认为是有充分理由的
includes many useful new features its
包括许多有用的新功能
modernized to to leverage what Java SE 8
现代化以利用Java SE 8
provides it's got support for the Java
提供对Java的支持
time api's repeatable annotations you
时间api的可重复注释
can apply constraints to collection
可以将约束应用于集合
elements to optionals and it has a host
可选元素，它有一个主机
of new constraints some of these were
一些新的约束条件是
already there and hibernate validator
已经在那里并且休眠验证器
and I think they had gotten a very
我认为他们已经得到了非常
positive reception there so the requests
那里的积极接待，所以要求
were made to add these into the standard
被制成将它们添加到标准中
beam validation as well so a host of new
光束验证以及许多新的
constraints so some of these passed
约束，所以其中一些通过了
repeating annotations when we did all of
当我们完成所有
these J SRS and the maintenance releases
这些J SRS和维护版本
that I'll be talking about we've been
我会说我们一直在
opportunistically introducing repeating
机会地引入重复
annotations we haven't read specs just
我们尚未阅读规格的注释
for the purpose of adding repeating
为了增加重复的目的
annotations but I think most of our J
注解，但我认为我们大多数J
SRS have undergone enough changes that
SRS已经进行了足够的更改，以至于
we've been we've been leveraging
我们一直在利用
repeating annotations so that's now
重复注释，现在
pretty consistent across the entire each
在每个方面都非常一致
platform constraints within container
容器内的平台约束
elements such as here where you want a
元素，例如这里您想要的
map of a valid customer and a valid
有效客户和有效客户的地图
account or with optionals the last
帐户或带有可选选项的最后一个
example here illustrates the the new
这里的例子说明了新的
annotations the fact that your list
注释您的列表
should not be empty at the result of
结果不应为空
this and that you want the customer
这个，你想要顾客
emails to be non blank strings that are
电子邮件为非空白字符串
configured appropriately as email
适当配置为电子邮件
addresses
地址
okay the new Java EE security API this
好的，新的Java EE安全API
is something that was requested for a
是要求
long time so there are a number of key
时间长了所以有很多关键
new api's that were added here I'm going
我要在这里添加的新api
to talk about these three security
说说这三个安全
context the HTTP authentication
上下文HTTP认证
mechanism API and identity stores so
机制API和身份存储区
part of the goal or a large part of the
目标的一部分或大部分
goal is simplification of security in
目标是简化安全性
Java EE common approaches common
Java EE通用方法通用
mechanisms and leverage of CDI to
CDI的机制和杠杆作用
specify one how these work and two how
指定一个如何工作，两个指定
they're configured so security context
它们被配置为安全上下文
this has methods for authentication
这有验证方法
authenticate would be used in the web
身份验证将在网络中使用
tier get color principle and get
层获取颜色原理并获取
principles by typing is call a role if
键入的原则称为角色
you're familiar with the servlet and EJB
您熟悉servlet和EJB
spec you'll notice that we didn't have
规格，您会注意到我们没有
uniform naming across these api's which
在这些api上统一命名
is you know generally a source of
您是否通常知道
confusion and typos I guess when you're
我猜你在困惑和错别字
trying to write your applications so
尝试编写您的应用程序，以便
these are intended to supersede the
这些旨在取代
existing inconsistently used method and
现有不一致使用的方法，以及
consistently named methods which of
一致命名的方法
course you can still you can still use
当然你仍然可以继续使用
so to have a common API across the
以便在整个
different container types the HTTP
不同的容器类型HTTP
authentication mechanism is designed
设计认证机制
specifically for the web tier for the
专门针对网络层
servlet container only it's modeled on
仅以servlet容器为模型
the jaspe server off module SPI but what
jaspe服务器关闭了模块SPI，但是
it is is it's an intended to capture the
这是为了捕获
just pick is quite powerful but it's
只是选择是非常强大的，但是
very complex and we've had you know
非常复杂，我们已经知道了
number of people concerned about the
关注人数
complexity the awkwardness to use so the
复杂性使用笨拙，所以
goal here is to provide something that
这里的目标是提供一些
is much more user friendly in terms of
在以下方面更加用户友好
how you how you use it how you define
您如何使用它如何定义
the
的
hey VIIRS so the key methods of this
嗨，VIIRS，这的关键方法
interface are validate request which is
接口是验证请求
provided to allow the caller to
提供给呼叫者
authenticate so you can extract this is
验证，以便您可以提取这是
called before due filter or cert or
在适当的过滤器或证书之前调用，或
service method so you can extract
服务方法，以便您可以提取
information from from the HTTP header or
来自HTTP标头的信息或
the request parameter and so on secure
请求参数等安全
response which is invoked as you might
您可能会调用的响应
expect after and that would allow you to
期待之后，那将使您能够
do things like I guess encrypting your
做类似我想加密你的事情
response if you want it to do something
如果您要它做某事，请回应
they're clean subject lets you clean up
他们是干净的主题，让您清理
get rid of any any caller specific
摆脱任何特定的来电者
information cookie state perhaps or
信息cookie状态或
anything else that would you would not
你不会做的其他事情
want to have propagated any further so
希望进一步传播
you could package this with the
您可以将其与
application you can package your own HTT
您可以打包自己的HTT应用程序
HTTP authentication mechanism
HTTP认证机制
implementation with the application or
与应用程序一起实施或
you can use a container supplied one and
您可以使用提供的容器
there are rules for the prioritization
有优先顺序的规则
of these and the configuration of these
这些和这些的配置
so this api in turn can delegate to the
因此此api可以委托给
identity store api which is used to
身份存储api用于
interact with the stores that have user
与有用户的商店互动
information both for authenticating and
用于身份验证和
retrieving information like user group
检索用户组之类的信息
information the security API spec
信息安全API规范
identifies a number of types of identity
识别多种身份
stores I believe these are extensible so
商店，我相信这些都是可扩展的，所以
LDAP database there used to be embedded
曾经被嵌入的LDAP数据库
I'm not sure whether that got pulled or
我不确定这是被拉走还是
not in the final release you can find
不在最终版本中，您可以找到
out more in the security talk that's
在安全性讨论中可以了解更多
later in the conference but this is used
在会议的后面，但是使用了
for authentication or authorization or
用于身份验证或授权，或
both the main methods here are validate
这两个主要方法都是有效的
so you can validate a
这样您就可以验证
as to whether or not that is valid and
关于这是否有效，以及
the user can proceed or you can extract
用户可以继续进行，也可以提取
the caller the caller groups for further
呼叫者呼叫者分组以进一步
authorization if in fact that is
授权，如果实际上是
supported by the identity store identity
身份存储所支持的身份
stores can support authentication or
商店可以支持身份验证或
authorization or both and you can
授权或两者兼而有之，您可以
determine from the identity store which
从身份存储中确定哪个
it supports the HTTP authentication
它支持HTTP身份验证
mechanism can leverage multiple identity
机制可以利用多个身份
stores so it can go through several
商店，因此它可以经历几个
identity stores determining whether
身份存储确定是否
whether based on a credential the caller
是否基于凭证调用方
has the has the right to continue so you
有权继续，所以您
can combine the results of the identity
可以结合身份的结果
store the identity stores as they're
存储身份存储
produced so as I mentioned we did a
就像我提到的那样，我们做了一个
number of maintenance releases as well
维护版本的数量
JPA most of these are quite small JPA
JPA其中大多数都是相当小的JPA
was probably the the more significant
可能更重要
one of this list Java Mail had a number
此列表之一Java Mail中有一个数字
of small improvements common annotations
小改进通用注释
mentioned for priority and repeating
提到优先和重复
annotations interceptors was just a
注释拦截器只是一个
cleanup and WebSocket was done a while
清理和WebSocket完成了一段时间
ago we also completed a number of
以前我们还完成了一些
maintenance releases for Java SE 9 and
Java SE 9和Java的维护版本
these these are included in the
这些都包含在
glassfish reference implementation so
玻璃鱼参考实现
when you use GlassFish you'll see the
当您使用GlassFish时，您会看到
results of these but they're because
这些的结果，但它们是因为
these are SC api's they're not included
这些是SC API，不包含在内
as pursue in Java e8 per se which is
如Java e8本身所追求的那样
based on Java SE 8 so I promised our
基于Java SE 8，所以我向我们保证
team I talked about JP a.22 in
我在团队中谈到了JP a.22
particular what this adds is as
特别是这增加了
repeating annotation support I think JP
重复注释支持，我认为是JP
a was probably the the poster child for
一个可能是海报的孩子
annotations when it was released so I
发行时的注释，所以我
think they're now
认为他们现在
sixteen repeatable annotations and JPA
十六个可重复注释和JPA
support for date/time what we decided to
支持日期/时间，我们决定
do here was support mappings for those
在这里要做的是那些的支持映射
Java time types that are supported
支持的Java时间类型
underneath by JDBC we didn't want to get
在JDBC下面，我们不想得到
too massively created here creative here
过于庞大地在这里创作
with a lot of customizations but rather
有很多定制功能，但是
to build on what JDBC provided so namely
建立在JDBC提供的基础上
these five Java time supports local date
这五个Java时间支持本地日期
local time local date time and offset
当地时间当地日期时间和偏移量
time and offset date time and then the
时间和偏移日期时间，然后
ability to stream the result of a query
流查询结果的能力
execution so get results stream method
执行，以便获取结果流方法
added to both the query and typed query
已添加到查询和类型查询中
interface and then finally CDI injection
界面，然后进行CDI注入
into attribute converters we had
进入属性转换器
previously had CDI injection and entity
以前有CDI注入和实体
listeners but we had a number of
听众，但我们有很多
requests to add this to attribute
请求将此添加到属性
converters so that's also there okay so
转换器，所以也可以
where are we right now so we just
我们现在在哪里，所以我们只是
released September yay it's done finally
九月发布，它终于完成了
so this chart illustrates those api's
因此此图说明了这些api的
that underwent jsr new jsr s in Java EE
在Java EE中经历了jsr new jsr的
8 the ones in in dark blue our existing
8现有深蓝色
API s that were revved the ones in
修改过的API
orange down below these are new api's
在这些下方的橙色是新的api
that were added to the platform in Java
用Java添加到平台中
EE 8 if we look at the web profile which
EE 8，如果我们查看网站配置文件
is a subset notice the addition of both
是子集，请注意两者
Jason B and security comment about
杰森B和安全评论
security here the security API leverages
安全性，这里安全性API发挥了作用
the just pick servlet profile so we
只是选择servlet概要文件，所以我们
needed to add jaws pic also to the web
还需要在网络上添加下巴图片
profile but only the servlet
配置文件，但只有servlet
profile support is required okay so
个人资料支持是必需的，所以
where are we going well where we are
我们在哪里进展顺利
going is to eclipse so we're moving as
即将蚀，所以我们要像
you may well have heard we're moving
您可能已经听说我们正在搬家
Java EE to the Eclipse Foundation I
Java EE至Eclipse Foundation I
believe that the name of this is ee for
相信它的名字是ee
Jay at least that was the latest that I
杰伊，至少那是我最新的
heard and we have the great support of
听到了，我们得到了我们的大力支持
IBM and Red Hat in this move we
IBM和Red Hat在这一举动中我们
approached them first to make sure that
首先与他们联系以确保
just to validate that this was the right
只是为了验证这是正确的
direction and we got very strong
方向，我们变得非常坚强
agreement here we think that this will
我们认为在这里达成协议
lead to a more agile and flexible
导致更加敏捷和灵活
development process more open it will
开发过程会更加开放
allow things to move more quickly
让事情更快地移动
perhaps the details are still being
也许细节还在
worked out we expect we expect this
制定了我们期望我们期望这一点
process to go fairly quickly we're being
过程进行得相当快，我们正在
quite aggressive and trying to get this
相当激进，试图做到这一点
worked out so this is the future we
算了，这就是我们的未来
think it will be more open going forward
认为未来会更加开放
we've gotten a lot of positive feedback
我们得到了很多积极的反馈
on this move so there's a lot of
在这一步上，有很多
excitement and I think we're off to a
激动，我想我们要去
good start a couple of the details here
在这里开始一些细节
we're transitioning GlassFish the our
我们正在过渡GlassFish我们的
eyes the tcks the product docks the
盯着产品停靠的地方
mailing lists I think and Oracle will
我认为邮件列表，Oracle会
continue to be providing support through
继续通过以下方式提供支持
Java EE 8 - to our customers into the
Java EE 8-给我们的客户带来
community and then we're often running
社区，然后我们经常跑
under Eclipse so I'm just going to leave
在Eclipse下，所以我要离开
you with a couple of pointers here where
你在这里有几个指针
you can learn more if you want to stay
如果您想留下来，可以了解更多
in this room
在这个房间里
I notice that Ed Burns who is one of our
我注意到Ed Burns是我们的一员
spec leads for the servlet API and Ching
Servlet API和Ching的规范负责人
Y Chen have just come in so they're
陈刚进来的
going to be talking here about servlet 4
将在这里谈论servlet 4
oh if that's what interests you and then
哦，如果那是你的兴趣，然后
later today there's a panel discussion
今天晚些时候有一个小组讨论
on the moon
在月球上
of Java EE - the Eclipse Foundation so
EE的原理-Eclipse Foundation这样
participants from Oracle IBM Red Hat and
Oracle IBM Red Hat和
the Eclipse Foundation will be present
Eclipse Foundation将存在
there and then as the week goes on we'll
在那里，然后随着一周的进行，我们将
have other spec leads describe some of
还有其他规范线索描述了一些
the some of the new features of many of
许多的一些新功能
the other api's in this platform I'll
我将在该平台中使用其他API
put in a plug for the JCP buff tomorrow
明天为JCP的爱好者戴上插头
night that's going to include a number
夜晚将包括一个数字
of the spec leads I hope to be there as
的规格线索我希望能在那里
well where you can ask questions and
好，在那里你可以问问题和
interact more informally with members of
与以下成员进行更非正式的互动
the community so with that I don't know
社区，以至于我不知道
if I have time for any questions I think
如果我有任何问题的时间，我认为
I need to leave to get these guys set up
我需要离开让这些人成立
but I'll be in the hacker garden this
但是我会在黑客花园里
afternoon so if anybody wants to Corral
下午，所以如果有人想去科勒尔
me there I'd be more than happy to to
我在那里我很乐意去
meet with you and and answer any
与您见面并回答任何问题
questions so thank you
问题，谢谢